(ナルト)ふぅ…
危なく ペシャンコだったぜ。
Whoa, I was about to get flattened...
(フウカ)フフフフ… フエンの仕掛けも
たいしたことがないねぇ。
Fuen's traps are nothing special.
(地陸)これほどの使い手とは…。
I can't believe they're this skilled.
くっ！
もはや 我が手には負えぬか…。
I can't handle him anymore.
(フドウ)うぉ～っ!!
(ヤマト)やったか!?
Did I get him?
フフフフフ…。
効かん！
That won't work!
この！
Damn you!
ムダだ！
It's futile!
ちょこまかと…。
Scurrying about like that...
土遁 岩板柩！
Earth Style! Stone Plate Coffin.
終わったな。
It's over.
フン！ 墓標くらい建ててやるか。
I guess I can at least make him
a grave marker.
フフフフフ…。
チッ！ フエンの野郎のおかげで
汗 かいちまった。
I had to work up a sweat
on account of that jerk Fuen.
フッ… 自分の術を
過信しすぎなんだよ。
You place too much confidence
in your own Jutsu.
とどめの確認は
ちゃんとしないとね。
You have to make sure
you've finished the job.
《しかし… ヤツらの狙いはなんだ？
But what are they after?
遺体を盗み出したうえに
わざと目立つように逃げた…》
After stealing the bodies,
they intentionally attract
attention in their escape...
Are they after one of us
from the Leaf?
狙いは
ボクら 木ノ葉のうちの誰か？
とすると ダンゾウがらみか？
If so, is Danzo involved?
Impermanence
(サクラ)ふぅ… 敵の術中に
完全に はまったみたいね。
It appears we totally got caught
in the enemy's Jutsu.
(サクラ)まず みんなと合流しないと。
First, we must join up with the others.
きっと どこか 近くに
避難してるんだと…。
I bet they evacuated to
some nearby location.
えっ？
(ソラ)罰当たり野郎 捜してくらぁ。
Huh?!
I'm off to find that awful jerk.
ちょ… 待ちなさい！
Just a minute!
(ソラ)一緒に捜してても
しかたねえからさ！
There's no point to looking together.
ったく… 結局 全員
バラバラになっちゃったじゃない。
For crying out loud.
So in the end,
everyone's scattered all over...
はぁ…。
(サクラ)しかたないか。
I guess it can't be helped.
チームプレーの訓練を
受けてるわけじゃないだろうし。
It's not like he received
any training on teamwork.
そういえば
ナルトも赤点だったっけ。
Come to think of it,
didn't Naruto flunk that part?
なんだ アイツ？
What's the deal with her?!
(フウカ)あ～あ やだやだ 肉体労働。
Oh, boy. I hate...manual labor...
(フウカ)手間ヒマかけず 仕掛けに
任せるつもりだったのにさ。
And here the plan was to
let the traps do the work
without me having to get involved.
しようがないね…
ちゃっちゃと やっちゃおうか！
I guess I have no choice.
I'll take care of this.
フン… ちゃっちゃと
終わりにしてやらぁ！
I'll end this lickety-split!
いくぜ！
Let's go!
え～っ!?
What?!
お前 いきなり何すんだよ!?
What the heck are you doing
out of the blue like that?
あら？ 経絡からもれる
このチャクラの味…。
What?! This taste of Chakra leaking
from your Chakra Network.
キミ 珍しく
風の性質変化を持ってるのね。
So you've got the rare wind
Chakra nature, huh?
だったら 何だってんだよ！
So what if I do?!
私のコレクションになってみない？
How about becoming part
of my collection?
ん… え？
Hm?! Huh?
フレンチとソフト どっちが好み？
Do you prefer French or soft?
はぁ… それ 食いもん？
Are those foods or something?
(フウカ)ったく… 接吻のことよ。
They're kisses.
つまり…！
In other words...
You mean you're going to kiss me?!
チュ… チューするってことか!?
ウフフ… そう うぶな子ね！
Yes.
You're such an inexperienced boy.
ファーストキスは まだなのかしら？
You still haven't even
had your first kiss?
Yikes! What?!
Don't mess with me!
なめんなよ！
オレだって チューぐらい経験あらぁ！
Even I've had experience kissing!
相手は男だったけど…。
It was with a guy, though.
そう まあ どうだっていいわ。
I see. Well, whatever.
How about having lots of fun with me?
これから２人で
たっぷり楽しまない？
冗談じゃねえってばよ！
誰が テメエなんかの相手すっかよ！
Not a chance!
Who'd want anything to do with you?
Oh, my... I've been turned down...
あらやだ… フラれちゃった。
Hey, what's with her?!
なんだよ アイツ！
ああいうタイプは苦手だってばよ！
I'm not good with women like that!
ウフフフ… 女の誘いを
断るなんて いけない子！
You must not turn down a proposition
from a woman, kid!
逃 が さ な い…！
I-won't-let-you-get-away.
ダメ！ やめて…！
No! C-Cut it out!
屍鬼接吻…。
Reaper Kiss.
なにっ…!?
What?!
はずれ！ 残念でした！
You missed! Too bad!
ねえちゃんのチュー
ちょっと冷たかったけど➡
Your kiss was kind of cold, but soft.
やわらかかったってばよ！
おとなしくしてりゃ
気持よく あの世にいけたものを！
Here you could've gone to
the next world comfortably
if you'd just held still...
Well, guess which one of us is real!
さあて どれが本物でしょうか!?
私を怒らせてしまったね！
Now you've made me angry.
(フエン)ホホホ… これはね
幻術なんかじゃない。
This isn't a Genjutsu.
(フエン)私が設計し 作った地形を➡
I summoned the terrain
I designed and created
他の空間から呼び寄せた…。
from a different spatial environment..
(フエン)あなたは もう…➡
You can't escape now.
もう 逃げられない。
(サイ)敵の作ったフィールドで
戦うほど バカじゃない。
I'm not so stupid as to fight in
a field created by the enemy.
フン… 隠れてもムダムダ。
It's useless to hide.
私の目から逃れることは
できないわ。 だって…➡
You'll never be free from my eyes.
After all, you've already
got my mark on you.
あなたには すでに
私の印がつけられてる。
どこへ逃げようと
お見通しってわけ。
I can see right through you
no matter where you try to escape to.
フッ…。
《まいたか？》
Did I lose her?
早く… みんなと合流しないと。
I've got to join up
with the others quick.
フフフ…。
その道を選んだのね。
So you chose that path, huh?
なに!?
ボクの姿は ヤツからは
見えないはず…。
She shouldn't be able to see me.
なぜ 行く先々に 仕掛けが!?
Why?
Why are there traps wherever I go?!
フッ… 遊びは
ここまでに しといてあげる。
I'll bring the playtime
to an end here.
うわっ!?
(フエン)残念ね。
How unfortunate...
あなたの動きは➡
All of your movements appear
on this design drawing.
すべて この設計図の上に
記されているの。
土遁 岩窃棍！
Earth Style: Spears of Stone
とどめよ！
This is the finishing blow!
はっ！
忍法 超獣偽画！
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll
岩窃棍！
Spears of Stone!
逃げちゃったんだ…。
He got away.
…私を コケにするなんて。
I can't believe he made
a fool of me.
まぁ 私に
いっぱい食わせるなんて➡
Well, he might just be
on the right track
やっぱ いい線いってるのかもね。
since he was actually able
to outmaneuver me.
(ダンゾウ)フン！ こんな年寄りを➡
This isn't the time to be
standing guard over an old man.
見張っている場合でもなかろうに。
(シズネ)夜間通信？
A night transmission?!
(綱手)何だ それは？
What's that?
フクロウです。
シマフクロウの一種でしょうか。
It's an owl.
Is it a Blakiston's fish owl?
だからなぜ フクロウがいる！
I want to know what an owl
is doing here!
火ノ寺より 緊急の報せです。
Oh! It's an urgent report from
the Fire Temple.
墓荒らしを 追っていた
カカシ班が敵の罠にはまったらしく。
It seems Team Kakashi,
in pursuit of the grave robbers,
has been caught in an enemy trap.
それを早く言え！
Why didn't you say that sooner?!
１匹は片づけた。
I took care of one of them.
フン 私のはアンタの相手と違って
ちょっとは やる子だったのよ。
Unlike your opponent,
mine was a kid with some fight in him.
逃がしたか。
Did he get away?
ここは
私がつくった 完璧な迷路なの。
This is the perfect labyrinth
I have created.
まず 生きては出られないわ。
There's pretty much
no way to get out alive.
どうだかな。
I wonder.
This is just a precursor
of the traps to come.
まだまだ仕掛けは 序の口。
私の仕掛けから逃げられたら
拍手喝采ってとこかしら。
Maybe I'll give them a round
of applause
if they are able to escape
from my traps.
このにおいは 硫黄？
This smell... It's sulfur.
毒性はなさそうね。
It doesn't seem to be poisonous.
サイ！
Sai!
忍法 超獣偽画！
Ninja Art: Super Beast Scroll
サイ！
Sai!
サイ 動かないで。
Sai, don't move!
骨が折れてる。
You've got a broken bone.
ちょっと痛いけど 我慢してね。
This is going to hurt a bit,
but tough it out.
(サクラ)これで よしっと！
That should do it!
Now for the spider poison.
(サクラ)次は クモの毒ね。
毒性は弱いから心配ない。
It's of low toxicity,
so you don't need to worry.
すぐ解毒するわ。
I'll neutralize the poison right away.
あの… 感動しましたか？
Umm...were you moved?
えっ？
Huh?
感動したんですね。
You were moved, weren't you?
だから こんなこと。
That's why you're doing this...
なに？ それ。
What're you talking about?!
(サクラ)『自己犠牲の勧め』？
"Recommendations
for Self-Sacrifice"?!
はい。 人間関係 特に女性と
よりよい関係をつくるためには➡
Yes. In order to create better
personal connections,
with women in particular...
我が身を
なげうつことが効果ありだと。
it says it's effective to lay down
your life for someone.
やっぱり 有効なんですね。
ナルト君にもやってみようかな？
Maybe I'll try this with Naruto, too.
はぁ？ いい加減にしろ！
What?
Knock it off!
うあ～っ！
私を怒らせたのが
運のつきね 坊や。
Now that you've made me angry,
your luck has run out, boy.
おう！ 本気になったか？
Now you're serious?!
望むところだってばよ！
That's what I want!
Okay, bring it on.
ちゃっちゃと かかってこい！
さ～て 全員 いっぺんに
チュウできるかな？
Can you kiss all of us at once?
火遁… 鳳仙火の術。
Fire Style: Phoenix Flower Jutsu!
ウフフフ… しょせん 坊やだねぇ。
You're just a boy, after all.
さて 本物は どこに
隠れているのかしら？
Now, I wonder where the real one
is hiding.
やったか？
Did I get her?
なにっ!?
What?!
クソッ… どういうことだってばよ。
Damn it! What's going on?
確かに 手応えは
あったはずなのに…。
And here,
I'm sure I felt like I hit something.
(フウカ)アハハハハハ…。
(フウカ)土遁 岩隠れの術。
Earth Style: Hidden in Stones Jutsu!
ちょっとは やるようね。
It appears you've got
some fight in you.
改めて欲しくなったわ。
キミの風のチャクラ。
Now I want your wind Chakra
even more.
お前… 不死身なのか!?
Are you immortal?
オレの螺旋丸くらって
無傷なんて ありえねえ！
No way can you be unharmed
after getting hit by my Rasengan.
キミの攻撃は まだまだ甘いのよ。
Your attacks are still too soft.
それより 今度こそ
受けてもらうわよ。 死の接吻。
More importantly, this time for sure
you will receive my kiss of death.
うぅ… そう簡単には させねえよ。
I won't let you do that so easily!
まずは その減らず口
たたけないようにしてあげるわ。
First, I'll make it so
you can't talk back.
影分身の術。
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
(フウカ)あらあら 芸がないわね。
また影分身？
Oh, my. No artfulness at all.
More Shadow Clones?
それじゃ こちらは…➡
Then I'll go with...
水遁 邪の口。
Water Style! Mouth of the Serpent!
なんだ？
What?!
《アイツ…
火と土と水のチャクラ性質…》
She has earth, fire and water
Chakra natures.
《３つも持ってやがんのか》
She's got three of them?
雷遁 地走り！
Lighting Style: Earth Flash!
《なに!? 雷だと？
じゃあ ４つものチャクラ性質を…》
What?! Lightning?!
She's got four Chakra natures!
あっ… あぁっ！
(ソラ)あれは いってぇ…。
What the heck is that?!
(ソラ)何者だ？
Who're you?!
(フリド)お前が ソラか…。
会いたかったぞ。
So you're Sora, huh?
I missed you.
ウッ… アヒィ…。
(トントン)ブゥ。
(シズネ)ありがとう 大丈夫よ。
(ヤマト)重そうですね。
ヤマト隊長。 どうしました？
任務報告書を提出しに。
では ここにのせてください。
アハハ… 手伝いましょうか？
失礼します。
《まさか 書類が
こんなにあるとは…》
Damn it.
Mysteries of the female body, my foot.
Hair is the most important thing
to a woman, my foot!
えぇ～っ!?
I don't want to know anything
about stuff like that.
こちらの報告書にも
判を お願いしますね。
シズネ！ ちょっとは休ませな。
ダメです！ このあと
忍者登録書の確認➡
任務の受け付け 上層部との会議
大名との懇談会 それから…。
(綱手)わかった わかった！
火影様の仕事は 激務ですね。
みんな 面倒かけてくれるからな。
なかでも やっかいなのが…➡
御意見番のお守りだぁ～！
(シズネ)ウヒィ…。
(ヤマト)ウヒョヒョ…。